That's my car, right?
His.
I'm so excited about this.
My life just got a whole lot brighter.
With this one.
Cars are life, right?
Yes, sir.
Tomita, I'm buying a car!
Yay!
And I finally bought it!
Now let's take a look at the car I'm going to share with you today!
It's so cute!
Ta-da!
Jimmy Sierra!
I didn't pay any attention to it today, but it turned out to be the same color as the other one.
Finally!
Good morning!
Thank you for waiting for me!
Thank you very much for your patience!
Keys! Thank you for the key! I got the Intelliki!
Here's the inspection certificate!
That's awesome! It's hot!
The owner's manual has all the ports in it, so I'm sure there's a little bit of maintenance in there.
I'll take it for verification! Thank you!
It's my car today! Here it is! Yes!
Yes! Let's see!
It's cute!
It's so cute!
Oh, man! I'm so excited! Oh, man!
It opened because I have the key. Of course you do.
All I can say is, it's cute.
The antenna here is kind of cute, too.
Oh, you want to look at it from above?
I'm going to look at it from above, from above.
I'm so happy! That's my car! It's my car!
But really, I just signed a contract here a couple of weeks ago, and I've been looking forward to it so much.
I'm so excited about it, and it's really brightened up my life.
Something about this one car. Of course, it's a big purchase.
It was one of the reasons for me to realize that there are so many fun things in life.
So I decided to do my best every day for something I can do what I like.
Cars are life, aren't they?
Yes!
Shall we go for a ride?
I'm going for a ride! The driver's seat!
It's my car now.
Cute sound, I love it all.
Ta-da!
Excuse me.
Wow!
Wow, but it still feels a little different than when I got in the car the other day.
It's my car now, right?
Our car.
It's our car, right? Oh, my God.
Let's go.
Shall we go?
Where shall we go?
Enoshima?
Yes, that's a lie. I'd like to go around the parking lot.
I'd like to change the angle of the mirrors
I'm going to change the angle of the mirrors by myself.
Okay, then.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Let's go, baby!
I'm driving. Wow.
Oh, but it's a little different than the other day when we were parking and driving.
Wow, I'm kind of nervous.
Wow.
Okay, so you're gonna end up over there.
And park.
Go? Park.
Okay, where do I park?
I don't know if I can make it.
Let's go.
Oh, where should we park?
I'll just park here.
But there's a back-up monitor, right?
Oh, I'd like to go there.
Can we go there?
I don't think I can make it.
I don't think I can go.
Let's just keep going down.
Maybe we could do it this way.
It's heavy if we do it like this, right?
It's pretty, pretty heavy, isn't it?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's heavy, isn't it? It's fine.
A little bit more.
Let's just step forward a little bit.
I can't get in one shot.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
It's the first time.
That's what happens.
It's coming back.
Wait. Oh, shit.
Hey, is it still to the right?
Just go this way.
This way, this way, this way.
How's that?
Well, well, well.
That was my first time parking a Sierra in a gym.
What do you think?
I'm so bad at it, I'm laughing my ass off, but I'm surprised.
It's a little embarrassing.
A little embarrassing.
Well, it's just practice... I'm going to drive it a lot, and I'm going to do a lot of projects with it.
I would like to customize the interior in my own way, and I would like to do various projects such as driving plans.
I think I will be able to make a lot of new projects with the car from now on, so please look forward to them!
I'm going to enjoy the Jimmy Sierra life!
Please give me high ratings and subscribe to my channel!
If I don't succeed in getting the ride height adjustment today, I won't be able to buy this car.
I'm not qualified to buy this car.
I'm going to practice a little bit.
I'm off!
It's so different from what I expected!
The moment it's my car, I feel like...
What do you do?
I think it's also important to know where to put the car.
Now, I, Suzuka Tomita, would like to give you a voice-over from here.
I had never parked a car before, and parking was my least favorite thing to do.
Oops! Mr. Tomita!
Tomita, you are in the box almost next to the left line.
I think the highlight of Tomita's performance will be how he recovers from this situation.
I like the way she is looking at me.
Try to feel like you are in the girl's seat!
I wonder why I'm going there.
The direction to turn the steering wheel must be totally different
I can see it from an objective point of view.
It's hard to get a sense of what it's like to ride in a car, but it's also hard to get a sense of what it's like to ride in a car.
The way you turn the steering wheel is completely different.
He looked like he was doing well.
Can you recover from this, Mr. Tomita?
Let's pull over a little more to the right.
It's definitely the wrong direction to turn the wheel, isn't it?
Why, why, I don't understand.
Mr. Tomita is in a bit of a quandary. What will happen to his car life in the future?
If I can't park, I can't go anywhere.
He has made a daring move to move back.
It's a bit off, isn't it?
Parking while looking at the rear-view monitor is a bit...
He looks so smug, but Oya's back was totally off.
There you go again!
I can't believe it.
One more time? Let's go one more time.
I'll never get used to this... the feeling of riding in this car.
Now, I'd like to make the most of the parking lot for my third try.
I'm not sure if there is no car next to me or not, but I have an excuse that it is hard to get in.
But how about a girl looking in the side mirror while looking in the side mirror?
Are you into it?
I wasn't used to looking in the side mirror and using the rear-view monitor.
So I used the side mirror and put it in. It went in in one shot! That's what I'm talking about!
See! That's a woman who knows what she's doing!
I'm Suzuka Tomita!
Isn't it amazing?
I'm gradually getting a feel for the body of this car.
I've done a couple of laps here, maybe 4 laps there.
I'm so happy! Now I can go home!